mozdev.org 2008-05-14

# mozdev.org - www: community/privacy

Mozdev Community Organization, Incorporated, a New York Not-for-Profit corporation ("mozdev") respects the privacy of every individual who visits mozdev's Web Site ("You") currently located at www.mozdev.org (the "Site"). This privacy statement covers the Site and outlines the information that mozdev may collect and how it will use that information. mozdev reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time by posting a new privacy statement at this location. Therefore, You are responsible for periodically checking the privacy statement for changes.

**1\. Information Collection and Use.**

mozdev will not collect any personally identifiable information about You - such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address - unless You provide it to mozdev voluntarily and approve its use.

If You do not want Your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to mozdev. When You do provide mozdev with personally identifiable information, it may use that information to better understand Your needs and how it can improve its products and services. mozdev may also use that information to contact You, for example, to answer a question or respond to a comment You have submitted. mozdev reserves the right to display any questions or comments You submit, without reference to your identity, together with any responses mozdev provides, on its frequently asked questions page found at <http://www.mozdev.org/faq.html>. In the case of requests for new projects, mozdev will use Your information to assess Your request, to verify Your identity and the identity of Your other project contributors, and for any other reasonable purposes in connection with Your request. However, it will not provide Your information to third parties without your consent, except as required by law as explained in the "Information Sharing" section below.

In some cases, mozdev may collect information that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system You use, the date and time You visited the Site, the pages You accessed, and the name of the web site from which You linked to the Site. mozdev uses this information to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**2\. Mailing Lists and Newsgroups.**

The Site hosts opt-in mailing lists and newsgroups for discussion about projects and for general issues related to Mozilla application and extension development. Opt-in mailing lists may be found on the main site at <http://www.mozdev.org/mailing-lists.html> and on the individual project pages. These mailing lists are bonded, which means they do not provide Your email address to third parties. If You have signed up for an opt-in mailing list and You later wish to opt-out, You may do this by following the instructions on the "mailing list" links on the relevant pages.

When you sign up on a mailing list on the Site, you may be sent newsletters and other announcements of interest to mozdev, depending on which mailing list you opt-in to. For a description of the non-project specific mailing lists available, please go to <http://www.mozdev.org/mailing-lists.html>.

You may have the opportunity to send an email to another user or mailing list, in which case Your valid email address and real name will be included in such messages. In order to prevent abuse, You may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from transmitting the email message.

When participating in newsgroups or chat rooms, Your personal information may be publicly available through Your profile display, in which case You have the option to opt-out of publicly displaying Your real identity. Where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at Your discretion and may be changed at any time by You.

The Site is an open source site and the data and information hosted on the Site is publically accessible by design. Anonymous messages (or posts that have been edited to be made anonymous) are against the spirit of open source. When You offer content for other mozdev users to read, attaching Your name to it gives other mozdev users the ability to reply to You privately about it, in case they feel that a public reply would be inappropriate. If You want to avoid spam, use mail filters, or refrain from posting on the Site. mozdev will not be responsible for any unsolicited email that You receive as a result of You posting Your email address on the newsgroups, chat rooms, or mailing lists.

This privacy policy does not protect any information that You transmit to newsgroups, chat rooms, mailing lists or other users.

**3\. Cookies.**

mozdev may use "cookies" - pieces of data stored on your computer tied to information about You - on the Site. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and will help mozdev enhance its web experience by saving time on the Site. With most Internet browsers, You can erase cookies from Your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to Your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

**4\. Information Sharing.**

Although mozdev makes every effort to preserve user privacy, it may need to disclose information when required by law wherein it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on the Site.

**5\. Certain Third Party Transactions.**

mozdev may disclose personal information to third parties it engages to provide services that involve data processing on its behalf. Also, if some or all of the assets of mozdev are sold to a third party, such third party will be entitled to use the personal information disclosed by You, but only in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

**6\. Security.**

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under mozdev's control. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of information You disclose online since a sufficiently powerful attack from an unauthorized third party could compromise your data.

**7\. Links to Non-mozdev Sites.**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that mozdev is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. mozdev encourages You to be aware when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site.

**8\. How to Contact mozdev.**

If You have any questions or suggestions regarding mozdev's privacy policy, or if You have submitted personally identifiable information through the Site and would like access to such information or to have that information corrected, please [email us](http://www.mozdev.org/feedback.html) or contact David Boswell at

Mozdev Community Organization  
Nigel L. Howard  
Covington & Burling LLP  
The New York Times Building  
620 Eighth Avenue  
New York, NY 10018-1405 

For questions or comments _not_ about a specific project, and _not_ covered in the [FAQ](http://www.mozdev.org/faq.html), please read our [feedback](http://www.mozdev.org/feedback.html) page.  
[Copyright](http://www.mozdev.org/copyright.html) © 2000-2008. All rights reserved. [Terms of Use](http://www.mozdev.org/community/terms.html) & [Privacy Policy](http://www.mozdev.org/community/privacy.html).
